Guide to the Business Office, Yale School of Drama, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Business office, Yale School of Drama, records
1956-1987
RU 729
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
30.75
(49 boxes)
The records consist of invoices, financial statements, contracts, publicity materials, tax forms, and subscription files documenting the business office of the Yale School of Drama.
Yale School of Drama
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-E (YRG 22-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Drama.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of invoices, financial statements, contracts, publicity materials, tax forms, and subscription files documenting the business office of the Yale School of Drama.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Finance; Yale School of Drama; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Finance
- Records of the Business Office, 1956-1982; Accession 1986-A-026
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2017
  - ABC Fellows, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ABC Films, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ABC Program: General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Accounts Memoranda, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acting Company: Budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acting Department, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Actors Equity, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Contracts, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Actors Equity Contracts: (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Actors Equity: Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Actors Equity: Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Policies, Rules, General Information, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Security Agreements and Guarantees, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Advertising for Subscription Campaign, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Affirmative Action, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Agreements between Actors Equity and League of Resident Theatres, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - "The Alchemist": Costs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Aliens, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Alteration Requests, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Alterations, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Alterations: Maintenance and Repair, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - American Educational Theatre Association (AETA) Convention, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - American National Theatre and Academy (ANTA), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Amusement License, 1965-1971 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Audio-Visual Center, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Auditions, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Authorizations, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - B Correspondence, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - "Birthday Party": Production Costs, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Black Arts Theatre Group, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - "A Black Quartet", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Black Reality Players, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Black Student Recruiting, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Black Workshop, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - List of Books Added to Drama Library, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Box Office, 1957-1968 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Box Office Analysis, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Box Office: Miscellaneous, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Box Office Receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Box Office Sales Reports, 1982-1974 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - "Brown": Production Costs, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Brochures, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Brochures and Programs, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Brochures, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Budgets: Memos and Correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Budgets, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Projected Theatre, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Budget Expenses and Projections, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Budget, Projected Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Budgets, Theoretical Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Budget, Projected, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Budget: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Budgetary Information, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Memos on Budgets/Instructions, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Budget Report, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Budget: Production Expenses, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Budget, Projected, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Budgetary and Financial Information, Ticketron Information: "Frogs", 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Budget: 20% cut, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Budget, Proposed, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Budget Accounts: Cabaret, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Budget: Expense Accounts, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Budget, Revised, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Budget Support, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Budget Data, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Budgets, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Budgets, Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Budget II, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Budgets: Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Budget: Internships, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Budgetary Footnotes, undated (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Building Renovation, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - "Camino Real": Expenses and Contracts, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Carpenters, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Casting, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Charity, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Children's Theater, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - "Chronicles of Hell": Box Office Statements, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Committee of 21, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Company Inquiries, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Computer Meeting Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Contibutions, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - "Coriolanus": Box Office Statements, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Costume Shop, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Costumes, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Courtesy Ticket Policy, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Davenport College: Play Analysis Class, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Delavallade, Carmen, Bill Evans Trio Concert, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Design, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Designers Seminar, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Development, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Directing Department, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Distribution Expenses, 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Drama Productions, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Drama School: Alumni Affairs, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Drama School Account File, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Drama School Re-Direction Coordinating Committee, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Drama School: Year-End Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Drama School: Miscellaneous, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Drama Students Guide, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - Dramat, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - John Drew Summer Theatre, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - Dunhill International List Co., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - "Dynamite Tonite!": Expenses, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - East West Foundation, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Educational Direction, Inc., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Embassy Pictures, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Employee Relations Department, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Employment Positions: Placement, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - "Endgame": Contracts, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Production Costs, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Endowment, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Energy Conservation, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Ensemble Company, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Ensembles, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - "Epiphanies": Expenses, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 175)
  - Equipment, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 176)
  - Equipment and Summer Renovations, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 177)
  - Equity Forms: General, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 179)
  - Ezra Stiles College, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 180)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 181)
  - Faculty: General, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 182)
  - Fence Club, 1973, 78 (Box 10, Folder 185)
  - Film Course, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 187)
  - Film Program, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 189)
  - Financial Aid, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 190)
  - Financial Records, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 191)
  - Financial Report, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - Financial Statements
    - 1956-57 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - 1957-58 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - 1958-59 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 201)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 202)
    - 1967 (Box 11, Folder 203)
  - Fire Inspection and Building Code Inspection, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 204)
  - Fire Marshal, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 205)
  - Firemen's Service, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 206)
  - Follow-Up Reading File, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 207)
  - Footnotes to Budget, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 208)
  - Ford Foudnation Survey, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - Foreign Faculty, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 211)
  - Form Letters: (Box 11, Folder 212)
    - Use of the Bank, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 213)
    - Gymnasium, 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Yale Shuttle, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 215)
    - Holiday Inn, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 216)
    - Library, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 217)
  - Form Samples, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 218)
  - The Fourth International Congress on the Enlightenment: "Rameau's Nephew" and "La Buona Figliola", 1975 (Box 11, Folder 221)
  - Freshman Letter, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 222)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 223)
  - General Brochures, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 225)
  - General Funds, 1959-1969 (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - General Requisitions, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 227)
  - Gielgud-Worth Expenses, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 228)
  - Gifts to the Drama Department, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 229)
  - "Glass Menagerie" Workshop I: Box Office Statements, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 231)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 232)
  - Graphics, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 234)
  - "Greatshot": Expenses and Contracts, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 235)
    - Script, undated (Box 12, Folder 236)
  - Greece, Consul General of, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - Greenwich High School, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - Group Ticket Sales, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 239 - 240)
  - Guthrie Theatre, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - Hamlet: Production Costs, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - Handicapped Accessibility, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - Handicapped, undated (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - Harold Lloyd Film Festival, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Hartford After Dark, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - Hartford Stage Company, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - "Henry IV": Box Office Statements, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 250)
  - Hill Theatre Project, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 251)
  - "Holzmann" Workshop 5: Box Office Statements, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 252)
  - Housekeeping Division, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 253)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 254)
  - House Manager and Box Office Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 255)
  - House Reports: Major Productions, 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - House Scaling, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 257)
  - Housing, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - Mel Howard Productions, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 260)
  - Illinois Arts Council, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 261)
  - "The Inheritors": Contracts, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 262)
  - Inquiries, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 263)
  - Insurance, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 264)
    - 1968 (Box 13, Folder 265)
  - Inventory, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 266)
  - Inventory Forms, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 267)
  - Inventory and Equipment Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 268)
  - Island Repertory Theatre: Contracts, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 269)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 271)
  - "James and the Giant Peach", 1971 (Box 13, Folder 272)
  - Japanese No Troupe Expenses, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 273)
  - Job Applications (Box 13, Folder 274)
  - Job Applicants and Temporary Help, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 275)
  - Job Description: Shop Technician, undated (Box 13, Folder 276)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 277)
  - "Kelley's Eye" Workshop 2: Box Office Statements, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - Key Matters, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 284)
  - "Kid Twist", 1976 (Box 14, Folder 285)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 290)
  - League of Professional Theatre: Training, undated (Box 14, Folder 293)
  - League of Resident Theatres (LORT): Conference, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - General Information, 1974-1979 (Box 14, Folder 295)
    - Minutes, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - Legal Matters, undated (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - Letters of Acknowledgement for Costume Donations, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 299)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - License Fees, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - Lighting, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - Lighting and Costume Budgets, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 305)
  - Lighting Equipment, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 306)
  - Lighting Matters, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 307)
  - Liquor Permit, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 308)
  - Literary Manager, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 309)
  - "Little Malcolm" Workshop 3: Box Office Statements, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 310)
  - Long Wharf Theatre, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 311)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 313)
  - Machine Contracts, 1972-1976 (Box 15, Folder 314)
  - "Mahagonny", 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 315)
  - Mailing Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Maimonides Institute, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 317)
  - Main Stage Productions, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Major Productions: Expenses, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Management Students, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Manual of Procedure, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 321)
    - Addenda, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 322)
    - Final Corrections, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - McGee Concert, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Mellon Foundation, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 325)
  - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 326)
  - Mime Troupe, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 327)
  - "Much Ado About Nothing": Expenses, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 328)
  - Murry Lewis Dance Company, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 329)
  - Music School, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 330)
  - N Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 331)
  - National Arts Council, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - National Committee for Cultural Resources, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 333)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 334)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 335)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 336)
    - Budgets and Information, 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 337)
    - Internship Program, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - National Ticket Company, 1958-1968 (Box 17, Folder 340)
  - NBC, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 341)
  - Negro Ensemble, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 342)
  - New America Theatre Ensemble, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 343)
  - New England Theatre Conference News, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 344)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 345)
  - New Haven Civic Ballet, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 346)
  - New Haven Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 347)
  - New Haven, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 348)
  - New York Benefit for Drama School, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 350)
  - Nikolais Dance Theatre, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 351)
  - O Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 352)
  - Office of the Provost (Charles Taylor), 1966 (Box 17, Folder 353)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 354)
  - "Operation Sidewinder": Contracts, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 355)
  - Outside Booking Possibilities, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Oxford and Cambridge Shakespeare Company, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - P Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 359)
  - Paid Advertising, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 360)
  - Pantagleize, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 361)
  - Paramount Theatre, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 362)
  - Parking, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 363)
  - Parking for Subscribers, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 364)
  - Patron of Young Audiences, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 365)
  - Patrons, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 366)
  - Personnel, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 368)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 369)
  - Photography, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 370)
  - Poco Productions, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 371)
  - Police Reports, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 372)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 373)
  - Policies: Miscellaneous Outside Jobs, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 374)
  - Polish Laboratory Theater (Grotowski, Jerzy), 1968 (Box 18, Folder 375)
  - Press, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 378)
  - Press List, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 379)
  - Press/Publicity, 1972-1977 (Box 18, Folder 380)
  - Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 381)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Press Releases about Plays, undated (Box 18, Folder 383)
  - Printing of Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Pro-Dance, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 386)
  - Production Budgets, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 387)
  - Production Crews, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 388)
  - Production Expenses, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 389)
  - Production Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 390)
  - Production Notebook: Originals, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 391)
  - Production Office Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 392)
  - Productions, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 393)
  - Program Advertising, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 394)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 395)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 396)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 397)
    - Rates and Contracts, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 398)
  - Programs, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - "Prometheus Bound", 1967 (Box 19, Folder 400)
    - Contracts, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 401)
  - Property Loss, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 402)
  - "The Proposition", 1970 (Box 19, Folder 403)
  - Props: Major # 1, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 404)
    - Major # 2, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 405)
  - Publicity and Press Relations: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 406)
  - Purchasing, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder 407)
  - Purchasing Matters, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Q-R Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 20, Folder 409)
  - Register Publishing Company, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 410)
  - Rehearsal Schedule, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 411)
  - Relations with Dramat, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 412)
  - Renovations to the University Theatre Sound System, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 413)
  - Rent Schedule, University Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 414)
  - Repertory Dance Theatre, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 415)
  - Repertory Tour in Egypt, 1978 (October) (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Repertory Touring: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 417)
    - Payroll Sheet, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 418)
  - Reports and Survey: Subscription Statistics, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 419)
  - Resumes, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - "The Revenger's Tragedy": Box Office Statements and Reviews, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 421)
  - Richfield Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 422)
  - Rockefeller Grant, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 424)
  - "Rodogune", 1976 (Box 21, Folder 425)
  - Gordon Rogoff (Associate Dean), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 426)
  - Room changes, Rehearsal, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 427)
  - Royalties, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 428)
  - Running Crews, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 430)
  - S Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 21, Folder 431)
  - Safety Violations, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 432)
    - 1979 (Box 21, Folder 433)
  - Sales Tax, Drama Concessions, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 434)
  - Scale of the House, undated (Box 21, Folder 435)
  - Scholarships, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 436)
  - School Shows, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 437)
  - Scripts, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 438)
    - 1978-1982 (Box 21, Folder 439)
  - Season, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 440)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 441)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 442)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 443)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 444)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 445)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 446)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 447)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 448)
  - Seating Plan (Reconstruction), 1970-1975 (Box 22, Folder 449)
  - Seats: Furniture Type, undated (Box 22, Folder 450)
  - Seven Springs Farm, Mt. Krisco, N.Y., undated (Box 22, Folder 451)
  - Show Expenditures, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 452)
  - Sound Equipment, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 454)
  - Space, 1973-1976 (Box 22, Folder 455)
  - Special Projects, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 456)
  - "S.S. Glencairn", 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 457)
    - Production Costs, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 458)
  - Space, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 459)
  - Stage Lighting Rental, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 460)
  - Stage Manager's Report, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 461)
  - Standing and Blanket Purchase Orders, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 462)
    - Report, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 463)
  - "Story Theatre", 1969 (Box 23, Folder 465)
  - Street Theatre, Inc.: Howard Stein, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 466)
  - Strong-Cohen Graphic Design, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 468)
  - Student Pass, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 469)
  - Student Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 470)
  - Subscriptions, 1950-1966 (Box 23, Folder 471)
    - 1961-1965 (Box 23, Folder 472)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 473)
  - Subscription Statistics, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Subscription Mailings, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 475)
  - Subscriptions, 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 476)
  - Subscription Statistics, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 477)
  - Subscription Report, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 478)
  - Subscription Campaign, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 479)
  - Subscription Expenses, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 480)
  - Subscription Campaign Ideas, 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 481)
  - Subscription Campaign, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 482)
    - Fall Brochure, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 483)
  - Subscriptions, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 484)
  - Subscription Campaign, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 485)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 486)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 487)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 488)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 489)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 490)
  - Summary of Income/Expenses, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 491)
  - Summary of Projected Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 492)
  - Summer Cabaret, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 493)
  - Summer Possibilities for Yale Repertory Company, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 494)
  - Sunday/Monday Series, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 495)
  - Sunday Series, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 496)
  - Survey of Arts Administration Programs, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 497)